Guide to the J. Arthur (Jesse Arthur) Younger Papers, 1951-1968
Department of Special Collections
- CONGRESSIONAL RECORD - clippings 196589th Congress
  - JUNE:
    - Arthur Hoppe's Satire on Washington, 6-21-65 (Page A3215)
    - Federal Cigarette Labeling and Advertising Act. JAY'S REMARKS, 6-22-65 (Page 13905)
    - Housing and Urban Development Act of 1965 JAYS REMARKS, 6-28-65 (Page 14331)
    - Behind 14(b) Repeal: Labor's Drive to Reform Taft-Hartley Has Political Motive, John A. Grimes, 6-28-65 (Page A3360)
    - Why L.B.J. Wants McKee, Robert Allen & Paul Scott., 6-28-65 (Page A3371)
    - Gobernment by Guideline: A New Threat to Economic Freedom, George Champion., 6-29-65 (Page A3414)
  - JULY:
    - The Misguided Mishmash, Terrence O'Flaherty., 7-7-65 (Page A3587)
    - A New Class to Lead the Poor, Lawrence Fertig., 7-9-65 (Page A3648)
    - JAY'S REMARKS Amendment to the Atomic Energy Act of 1954, 7-12-65 (Page 15761)
    - Professors Were to Blame for Berkeley Mess, Hon. Max Rafferty., 7-12-65 (Page A3689)
    - Federal Cigarette Labeling and Advertising Act. JAY'S REMARKS., 7-13-65 (Page 15963)
    - Two Articles From Young Voice, Karen Setterfield & Kathy Leonard., 7-20-65 (Page A3907)
    - Some Observations on the So-Called New Economics, Raymond Saulnier., 7-26-65 (Page 17489-91)
    - THe Unseen Drama, Joseph Aslop, Wash. Post, 7-26-65 (Page A4057)
    - Patman Jabs at Martin Carry Little Weight, Thomas J. Foley., 7-27-65 (Page A4124)
    - Amendment to Section 271 of AEC Act of 1954 JAY'S REM, 7-28-65 (Page 17953)
    - Tribute to The Honorable Joseph Campbell JAY'S REMARKS, 7-28-65 (Page 17964)
    - Amendment to Section 72271 AEC JAY'S REMARKS, 7-29-65 (Page 17998-99, 18002-6)
    - Views on Congressional Action, Gilmore, Wilson & Lawren, 7-29-65 (Page A4183)
    - Supreme Courts Rulings a Factjo in Losing Crime Way R. Collings, Jr., 7-29-65 (Page A4192)
  - AUGUST:
    - Government Control of Economy No Good for US or Western World, John A. Davenport, 8-4-65 (Page A4315)
    - Military Construction Appropriations Bill, 1966 JAY'S REMARKS., 8-10-65 (Page 19121)
    - Joint Labor-Management Programs, JAY'S REMARKS, 8-10-65 (Page 19143)
    - Mistakes of the Great Society, Richard Wilson., 8-10-65 (Page A4430)
    - The German Resistance in American Perspective, Karl Brandt., 8-13-65 (Page 19610-13)
    - Castro Threat not so empty, Marguerite Higgins, 8-23-65 (Page A4701)
    - Beyond the Los Angeles Terror, Wall Street Journal., 8-23-65 (Page A4704)
    - Lyndon Johnson Today, Laurence M. Stern., 8-31-65 (Page A4909-11)
  - SEPTEMBER:
    - Needed: New Approach to Expenditure Evaluation, Charles L. Schultze., 9-2-65 (Page A4977-78)
    - The Crisis in Vietnam, Art Hoppe., 9-3-65 (Page A4997-98)
    - We're Talking Too Much, Evening Star editorial., 9-8-65 (Page A5045)
    - A Bitter Legacy, Wall Street Journal, Press Prestidigitators, George Dixon, 9-14-65 (Page A5152)
    - The Phony Cry of Police Brutality, Judge Norman Elkington., 9-15-65 (Page A5194-95)
    - The Press Seems To Be Changing Its Point of View, Charles McCabe, 9-15-65 (Page A5204-05)
    - Accomplishments of Pan American Airways, JAY'S REMARKS, 9-16-76 (Page 23197-99)
    - Columnist Arthur Hoppe's Satire, Art Hoppe., 9-16-65 (Page A 5233)
    - Crisis in the Courts, Joseph Mathewson, 9-17-65 (Page A5273-74)
    - Phoney Baloney in Welfare Spending, Robert Freeman, 9-20-65 (Page 23510-12)
    - What'll Elbie Jay do for an Encore? Art Hoppe, 9-20-65 (Page A5290-91)
    - Failure in Southeast Asia? Bruce Lee, 9-20-65 (Page A5303-04)
    - Communism and You, Wackenhut Corp. Pamphlet., 9-22-65 (Page A5353)
    - Economist Sets Fatal Date, Sidney P. Allen, 9-27-65 (Page A5444)
    - L.B.J.'s Pedernales Press Service, Kike & Hoppe., 9-27-65 (Page A5456)
    - Last Straw, Says Farmer, Sacramento Union, 9-28-65 (Page A5480=81)
  - OCTOBER:
    - Convernment Employees Salary Comparability Act, JAY, 10-1-65 (Page 24751)
    - Home Rule, Arthur Hoppe, 10-1-65 (Page A5520)
    - Our Surrender Over the Panama Canal, James Kilpatrick., 10-6-65 (Page A5602)
    - L. B. J. Pushing Luck on the Hill, Richard Wilson., 10-6-65 (Page A5611)
    - Mr. Johnson Meets the Pope, Art Hoppe, 10-11-65 (Page A5698)
    - New Wave of Inflationary Sentiment: Sooner or Later Something's Got to Give, Robert M. Bleiberg, 10-11-65 (Page A5708)
    - Why Does Elbie Jay Give a Dam? Art Hoppe, 10-12-65 (Page A5733)
    - The True `Advancement of Colored People': How Is It To Be Accomplished?, 10-12-65 (Page A5742)
    - Riots in Watts, Calif., Mr. M. B. Jackson, 10-18-65 (Page 25956)
    - Hubert Horatio at the Bridge, Art Hoppe, 10-18-65 (Page A5768)
    - Discription of Riots in Watts, Calif., EW Bickel, 10-18-65 (Page 26267)
    - Release by Professor Upgren, `US To Go Bust Nov. 18, 1970', Prof. Arthur Upgren., 10-18-65 (Page 26267-69)
    - Impressions of U.S.S.R. and Four Satellite Countries, R. S. Chaffer., 10-18-65 (Page A5836)
    - Demonstrations on Weekend, Jerry LeBlanc., 10-19-65 (Page 26503-12)
    - Termination of the Bracero Law, JAY's REMARKS, 10-20-65 (Page 26764-65)
    - The Bracero Program, JAY'S REMARKS, 10-20-65 (Page 26780)
    - Mansfield's Warning to Johnson, Doris Fleeson, 10-20-65 (Page A5906)
    - The Faith of Free Men, J. Edgar Hoover, 10-21-65 (Page A5907)
    - Everybody in the Club, Lucius Beebe, 10-22-65 (Page A5947)
    - Silence on the Potomac, Rowland Evans and Robert Novak, 10-22-65 (Page A6023)
    - The Fighting 89th--A Nondocumentary, Arthur Hoppe, 10-22-65 (Page A6031)
    - Mr. Johnson Is in Stitches, Arthur Hoppe, 10-27-65 (Page A6178)
  - NOVEMBER:
    - Big, Beautiful Hunk of Skin, Charles McCabe, 11-2-65 (Page A6249)
  - JANUARY (Box Box 8-13)
    - Where Do We Go From Here, Richard G. Capen, Jr., 1/10/66 (Page 25)
    - The Great Boston Power Play, William Hines, 1/10/66 (Page A2-3)
    - Americans Have Not Been Told About Communism, Clelland Cole, 1/10/66 (Page A8)
    - On Throwing Tantrums, Wall Street Journal, 1/10/66 (Page A14-15)
    - If Improvement Is The Genuine Objective, Dr. John Howard, 1/10/66 (Page A26-27)
    - There Is a Time for Decision, Herbert V. Prochnow, 1/12/66 (Page 103)
    - Hour of Decision on Vietnam Near, David Lawrence, 1/13/66 (Page A94)
    - Intrigue in the War on Poverty, Carl T. Rowan, 1/13/66 (Page A100)
    - A Preposterous Jobless Pay Bill, S. F. Examiner and News Call Bulletin Editorial, 1/13/66 (Page A104)
    - Four Columns by Art Hoppe, 1/17/66 (Page A157)
      - Greetings, Tax Fans
      - Jud Joad's Choice
      - Hubert Goes Away to Come Back
      - The State of Elbie Jay's Union
    - Yellow Rose Calls White House, Miss Mary McGrory, 1/18/66 (Page A169)
    - The HUD Headache, Rowland Evans and Robert Novak, 1/18/66 (Page A174)
    - Murphy's Law Catches Up With L.B.J., John Chamberlain, 1/18/66 (Page A180-181)
    - Democrats' Campaign Fund Reports Puzzling, Walter Pincus, 1/18/66 (Page A182-183)
    - Wage, Cost Increases Likely To Be Central 1966 Economic Issue, Dr. Leslie C. Peacock, 1/19/66 (Page A197)
    - Two-Year Terms, or Three or Four? James J. Kilpatrick, 1/19/66 (Page A209)
    - Why the Silence? San Mateo Times, Editorial, 1/20/66 (Page A247)
    - Our Man Hoppe: Private Drab Contemplates War, Art Hoppe, 1/24/66 (Page A272)
    - Johnson and Party Repairing Image, Walter Pincus, 1/24/66 (Page A280-281)
    - The Dangers of Leviathan, Lawrence Fertig, 1/25/66 (Page A327-328)
    - What Is Happening To The Spirit of America, Ed Hiles, 1/26/66 (Page 1069-1071)
    - Democratic Dismay, R. Evans and R. Novak, 1/26/66 (Page A353-354)
    - On Being Serious, Joseph Alsop, 1/26/66 (Page A357-358)
    - Half a War, Editorial, Washington Post, 1/26/66 (Page A360-361)
    - Budget's Brinkmanship, Richard F. Janssen, 1/31/66 (Page A419-420)
    - Where is L.B.J.'s Old Realism? John Chamberlain (Page A421-422)
  - FEBRUARY
    - Vietnam: The Perimeter Theory, Max Freedman, 2/2/66 (Page A450)
    - Why the Reserves? Joseph Alsop, 2/2/66 (Page A456)
    - Judge Damns U.S. Drift, M. K. Caldwell, 2/7/66 (Page A539)
    - Components of the Great Society, Richard Wilson, 2/7/66 (Page A541)
    - Who's Kidding Who? J. J. Miller, 2/7/66 (Page A547)
    - Again, A New War, Joseph Alsop, 2/7/66 (Page A552)
    - Elbie Jay Plans A Marrying, Art Hoppe, 2/7/66 (Page A556)
    - Veto Power Over Federal Reserve Would Remove Congressional Control and Destroy System, A. Sproul, Sr., 2/9/66 (Page A648)
    - Railway Labor Act Amendments, Discussion of., 2/9/66 (Page 2634-2643)
    - Profits and Freedom, Ben Wooten (Dallas Savings and Loan), 2/21/66 (Page 3337)
    - Fair Trial and Free Press, Raymond Spangler, 2/21/66 (Page 3339)
    - Got Problems? Learn to Share, Art Hoppe, 2/21/66 (Page A847)
    - Johnson Inscrutability Sparks Flap, Charles Bartlett, 2/23/66 (Page A903)
    - Elbie Jay, Arthur Hoppe, 2/23/66 (Page A917)
    - Big Government - Friend or Foe? Roger A. Freeman, 2/24/66 (Page 3890)
    - Can L.B.J. Afford This Engagement? Arthur Hoppe, 2/28/66 (Page A1001)
    - Is Confusion a U. S. Secret Weapon? Carl T. Rowan, 2/28/66 (Page A1009)
    - The Greatest Danger on Vietnam, David Lawrence, 2/28/66 (Page A1013)
  - MARCH
    - Speakers or Spectators, Ernest S. Marsh, 3/1/66 (Page 4308)
    - Congressman Mailliard's Address to Commonwealth Club, 3/1/66 (Page A1062)
    - Capitol Punishment, Art Buchwald, 3/2/66 (Page A1094)
    - Post Editorial, Rowland Evans and Robert Novak, 3/3/66 (Page A1120)
    - Address of Daniel P. Loomis, World Railroad Renaissance, Daniel Loomis, 3/7/66 (Page A1219)
    - Why Fulbright As Chairman? Gould Lincoln, 3/7/66 (Page A1226)
    - Agricultural Report, Council of California Growers, 3/8/66 (Page A1273)
    - Bay Area's New Left Connections With U. S. Old Left, Ed Montgomery at Commonwealth Club of S.F., 3/8/66 (Page A1287)
    - Johnson's Leadership, Joseph Alsop, 3/10/66 (Page A1356)
    - Reserves Could Have Speeded War, Richard Fryklund, 3/10/66 (Page A1363)
    - An Irrelevant Opposition, Editorial, Wall Street Journal, 3/14/66 (Page A1407)
    - The Northern Bombing, Joseph Alsop, 3/16/66 (Page A1491)
    - An Address By Mr. Serafin G. Menocal, Commonwealth Club, 3/16/66 (Page A1504)
    - Tribute to John Baldwin (Mr. Younger's Remarks and Pastoral Prayer of Reverend Shick, 3/24/66 (Page 6347)
    - Commerce OK's Russia's Exports, Robert Allen and Paul Scott, 3/30/66 (Page A1806)
    - Elbie Jay Meets His Equal, Arthur Hoppe, 3/30/66 (Page A1814)
    - He Is Not Dead, Reverend Paul Ludwig, 3/16/66 (Page 5759)
  - APRIL
    - Impacted School Area Money Restored, 1-minute speech by Mr. Younger with articles included by R. Evans and R. Novak and Mr. Maurice L. Peterson of U. C., 4/4/66 (Page 7166)
    - Increase in Agriculture Products From Mexico, Council of California Growers, 4/4/66 (Page A1910)
    - The Uncuttable Growth, Wall Street Journal Editorial, 4/4/66 (Page A1912)
    - Use of War on Poverty Funds to Establish Cooperative Stores in the San Francisco Bay Area, 1-minute speech by Mr. Younger with letter from Mr. Shriver to Mr. C. Wilson Harder and letter by R. W. Howard., 4/5/66 (Page 7327)
    - Tri Quang Speaks Out, Joseph Alsop, 4/20/66 (Page A2150)
    - Private Enterprise and Public Responsibility In A Free Economy, George Champion, 4/25/66 (Page 8433)
    - The Modern Hero--Bold, Strong, and 3-A, Art Hoppe, 4/25/66 (Page A2209)
    - Vietnam Warriors Cheered by Children's Crayon Drawings, David W. Plank, 4/26/66 (Page A2230)
  - MAY (Box Box 8-14)
    - Tax-Exempt Bonds, 5/4/66 (Page A2389)
    - Some Universities Are Lopsided, Their Role--To Get Bigger, Bigger Contracts - Dr. R. G. Ham, 5/4/66 (Page A2396)
    - Relationship Between Capital, Labor, and Management, Robert E. Williams, 5/5/66 (Page 9499)
    - Mao Tse-tung Slaps His Belly and Cries, Dr. S. T. Tung, 5/5/66 (Page A2458)
    - Controlling the Economy in a Political Climate, Richard Wilson, 5/9/66 (Page A2486)
    - What We Really Want At U.N. Is Not Victory, But Success, Lord Caradon, 5/10/66 (Page A2506)
    - What Price The Great Society, Charles Stevenson, 5/10/66 (Page A2521)
    - Is Famine the Only Answer? William H. Draper, Jr., 5/11/66 (Page 9832)
    - Revolt Against Freedom, Evans and Novak, 5/12/66 (Page A2564)
    - Guerrilla Warfare, William S. White, 5/12/66 (Page A2576)
    - Johnson's Footwork Seems Not So Nimble, Kilpatrick, 5/16/66 (Page A2603)
    - New Version of Old Shell Game Charges, Kilpatrick, 5/16/66 (Page A2612)
    - Trade Expansion Begun by L.B.J., R. Allen & P. Scott, 5/16/66 (Page A2621)
    - Mr. Paul-Henri Spaak Discusses Vietnam & NATO, 5/17/66 (Page A2660)
    - It's A Grand Fallacy That Capitalism Is Responsible For Black Africa's Backwardness, George N. Crocker, 5/26/66 (Page A2867)
    - Department of Transportation, Mr. Morris Forgash, 5/31/66 (Page 11263)
    - Rusk Clarifies U. S. Policy, David Lawrence, 5/31/66 (Page A2922)
    - The Fable of the Great Big Bull, Arthur Hoppe, 5/31/66 (Page A2927)
    - Hospital Ship `Hope' Richard C. Thompson, 5/31/66 (Page A2928)
    - Must Fear of China Shackle Our Power in Asia, Francis Vivian Drake, 5/31/66 (Page A2931)
  - June
    - Our Loss of Self-Control and Our Cancerous Disease, Walter E. Spahr, 6/1/66 (Page A2975)
    - Marine Transportation, Norman Scott, 6/2/66 (Page 11599)
    - A Cabinet Level Department of Transportation--Streamlining the Government Process, M. Forgash, 6/6/66 (Page 11700)
    - A Dog's Life in The White House, Arthur Hoppe, 6/6/66 (Page A3027)
    - Birth Control Blunders, Evans and Novak, 6/6/66 (Page A3034)
    - Contrast of Journalism By the Press and By Electronics, Walter D. Scott, 6/7/66 (Page 11918)
    - Rehabilitation of Our Merchant Marine, Daniel Strohmeier, 6/8/66 (Page 11992)
    - Law and Morality, Reverend W. Paul Ludwig, 6/8/66 (Page A3095)
    - Let's Put Mergers In Perspective, Glen McDaniel, 6/13/66 (Page 12343)
    - L.B.J. and the Polls, Evans and Novak, 6/13/66 (Page A3162)
    - Intimidation in Bond Drive, Joseph Young, 6/14/66 (Page 12485)
    - A Business Is An Idea, Mr. Frederick R. Kappel, 6/14/66 (Page 12488)
    - Why Johnson's Popularity Erodes, David Lawrence, 6/14/66 (Page A3182)
    - Greatest Saving Bond Pressure Reported Put On Postal Employees, Joseph Young, 6/16/66 (Page A3249)
    - The Shifting Political Winds, Walter Lippmann, 6/16/66 (Page A3259)
    - A World Patent System, General Sarnoff, 6/21/66 (Page 13081)
    - Leadership Gap, Richard M. Nixon, 6/21/66 (Page A3313)
    - Effective Missile Defense Is Possible, Dr. Teller, 6/27/66 (Page A3415)
    - Tight Money, Wall Street Journal Editorial, 6/28/66 (Page A3447)
    - We Fight Rhodesian Independence but Bless African Black Dictatorship, Mr. Fred Buechner, 6/29/66 (Page A3493)
    - The Press and National Security, Clifton Daniel, 6/30/66 (Page 14254)
    - The Mortal Issue, William S. White, 6/30/66 (Page A3535)
  - July 1966 (Box Box 8-15)
    - A Letter of Approciation From an Ex-GI, Charles J. Shields, 7/11/66 (Page A3585)
    - Solution to Vietnam War--And Strategic Deterrence for Peace--Lies in Antimissile Nike-X Rear Admiral Chester Ward, U.S. Navy, retired, 7/11/66 (Page A3580)
    - Big Brother FDA CONTENDS IT KNOWS BEST, James J. Kilpatrick, 7/11/66 (Page A3589)
    - A Department of Transportation, Morris Forgash, United States Freight Co., 7/11/66 (Page 14306)
    - Federal Grants and the Decline of the Federal System, Roger A. Freeman, 7/12/66 (Page 14672)
    - We Know What We Are, But Know Not what We may Be, Herbert V. Prochnow, 7/18/66 (Page 15222)
    - LBJ's Tardy Action, Evans and Novak Washington Post, 7/18/66 (Page A3757)
    - Should We Change Our Electoral College? Lucile Hosmer, 7/26/66 (Page 16339)
    - LBJ's Crunch With Congress, Rowland Evans and Robert Novak, 7/27/66 (Page A3974)
    - Two Columns by Mr. Arthur Hoppe, 7/29/66 (Page A4002)
    - How Has Communist China Planned Use of its Human Resources? Dr. Yuan Li-Wu, 7/29/66 (Page A4012)
  - AUGUST 1966
    - Tax-Free Fund and Socialism, Lawrence Fertig, 8/1/66 (Page A4036)
    - Communications and the Knowledge Industry, Robert W. Sarnoff, 8/2/66 (Page 17067)
    - Flowers for the Wedding of Miss Luci Johnson--Correction of Bill Enomoto's telegram of Aug. 2, 8/3/66 (Page 17307)
    - Is Freedom Dead? Excerpts from a series of addresses by Richard G. Capen, Jr., 8/3/66 (Page 17349)
    - Remarks of Brig. Gen. Joseph W. Stilwell, Jr., 8/3/66 (Page A4095)
    - Two Columns by Arthur Hoppe, 8/5/66 (Page A4128-4129)
    - Containerization, Morris Forgash, 8/11/66 (Page 18290)
    - Elbie Jay, Arthur Hoppe, 8/11/66 (Page A4249)
    - Why All This Inflation, James Daniel, 8/11/66 (Page A4253)
    - Economic Policy Failing, Richard Wilson, 8/11/66 (Page A4254)
    - Strike Casualties Editorial Page of Evening Star 8/15/66 plus article: Washington Close-Up: Adversity Kneads a New Johnson -- by Paul Hope, 8/16/66 (Page A4325)
    - Statement by Frank Stanton (Pres. CBS) before Subcommittee on Communications of Senate Commerce Committee, 8/29/66 (Page A4573)
    - Answer to Suppose God is Black by Ambassador H.L.T. Taswell from South Africa, 8/30/66 (Page A4600)
    - LBJ Sets Up Little Cabinets- Allen Scott Column in N. Va. Sun of 8/31/66, 9/1/66 (Page A4631)
    - Not Necessary to Teach Patriotism - Max Rafferty, 9/1/66 (Page A4640)
    - Ford Foundation's Proposal for a Satellite System -- Richard Hough, 9/1/66 (Page X20775)
    - Johnson's Can-Do Reputation Hurt Despite Gains by Howard K. Smith, 9/6/66 (Page A4655)
    - Consistency in War Persuasion by Royce Brier, 9/6/66 (Page A4659)
    - Illustrating the Job Corps Vulnerabi- lity by Charles Bartlett, 9/6/66 (Page A4663)
    - Kennedy Ax On Yorty Cuts Two Ways, 9/6/66 (Page A4670)
    - The Businessman's Stake in the Population Problem by James F. Oates, 9/13/66 (Page A4775)
    - Federal Government Attempts to Aid Housing by Marriner S. Eccles, 9/13/66 (Page A4783)
    - Pilot's Grueling day described by Admiral Walker before Commonwealth Club, 9/14/66 (Page A4816)
  - SEPTEMBER, 1966
    - Goldman's Stumbling Exit, Novak and Evans column from Washington Post, 9/15/66 (Page A4814)
    - Two Art Hoppe columns - A Little Corner of Old Vietnam and Trying a Whopper in Peace Bid - San Francisco Chronicle, Sept. 9th, 9/15/66 (Page A4823)
    - A World Patent System - General David Sarnoff, RCA, before the Commonwealth Club, 9/19/66 (Page 22043)
    - Sermon of Reverend Elmer J. Broad, 9/19/66 (Page 22044)
    - It's Still the Nut Holding the Wheel Wm. Hine's column, Washington Post, 9/15, 9/19/66 (Page A4838)
    - U. S. Aid Pushes Gov. Ownership in Aided Countries, Philip A. Ray before Commonwealth Club, Sept. 9th., 9/20/66 (Page A4859)
    - Ambassador Lucet (Fr.) on Hoarding Gold before Commonwealth Club, 9/16, 9/28/66 (Page A4998)
    - Law Enforcement's Role in the Community, William L. Faulstich before the San Mateo County Insurance Brokers Association, October 7, 1966, 10/10/66 (Page 24924)
    - Elbie Jay Makes a Match -- column by Art Hoppe, S. F. Chronicle, 9/29, 10/10/66 (Page A5206)
    - Columbus Day Address by Mayor Francis P. Pacelli, Daly City, 10/17/66 (Page A5337)
    - Elbie Jay Goes Far for a Friend, column by Art Hoppe, S.F. Chronicle, Oct. 13, 1966, 10/17/66 (Page A5342)
    - All the News We See Fit to Print, column by Art Hoppe, S. F. Chronicle, Oct. 17, 1966, 10/19/66 (Page A5406)
    - Farewell to Congressman D. R. Billy Matthews, 10/20/66 (Page A5453)
    - Farewell to Congressman Joseph W. Martin, Jr., 10/20/66 (Page 27163)
    - Farewell to Congressman Howard W. Judge Smith., 10/20/66 (Page 26992)
  - JANUARY 1967 90th CONGRESS (Box Box 8-16)
    - Where We Stand, Address by Herbert V. Prochnow, President of the First National Bank of Chicago., 1/12/67 (Page H143)
    - The Inaugural message of Gov. Ronald Reagan, of California., 1/12/67 (Page H146)
    - Is the Bell Tolling for Free Enterprise? by Richard C. Capen, Jr., Director of Public Affairs of the Copley Newspapers, La Jolla, California., 1/12/67 (Page H147)
    - Fairplay fo Hanoi by Art Hoppe, December 28, 1966, S.F. Chronicle., 1/12/67 (Page A69)
    - Johnson on the Hill: An Unhappy Tuesday by James J. Kilpatrick, The Washington Star, 1/15/67., 1/16/67 (Page A99)
    - George Hamilton Deserves Our Help Elbie Jay Travels in Great Circles by Art Hoppe, 11/1/66 and 11/3/66 S.F. Chronicle, respectively., 1/16/67 (Page A104)
    - Home to Roost, Wall Street Journal, 12/9/66, 1/16/67 (Page A114)
    - Remarks, 1/17/67 (Page H261)
    - Credibility Gap, editorial in overseas paper titled Newsweek:, 1/17/67 (Page A124)
    - Crippling His `War on Crime' an editorial in the Evening Star, 1/16/67, 1/17/67 (Page A133)
    - The Cost of Greed, and editorial in the Wall Street Journal. 1/13/67, 1/18/67 (Page A153)
    - American Economy to Get'Breating Spell' an address by Ransom M. Cook., 1/18/67 (Page A164)
    - Politics at the University of California, by JAY., 1/23/67 (Page H456)
    - Jed Joad sees Action and Elbie Jay Heads `em Off, by Art Hoppe, S.F. Chronicle, 1/4/67, 1/23/67 (Page a197)
    - The Wrong Road for Social Security, an editorial in 1/21/67 issue of Bus. Week, 1/30/67 (Page A311)
    - Gay Times in Washington & A Ticklish Peace Talk, 2 articles by A Hoppe, 1/16 and 1/18 issue of S.F. Chronicle, 1/30/67 (Page A314)
    - Painful Percentages, an article by Vermont Royster in the Wall Street Journal, 1/26/67., 1/30/67 (Page A320)
    - * MANDATORY SANCTIONS AGAINST RHODESIA By J. Arthur Younger, 2/1/67 (Page H887-97)
    - Miss Lynda Bird Spoils the Game article by A. Hoppe in the 1/23/67 issue of the S.F. Chron., 2/2/67 (Page A422)
    - Zambia growing wary on Rhodesia Sanctions, an article in the 2/1/67 issue of the Washington Star, 2/2/67 (Page A 414)
    - Our Movable Debt Ceiling: from the Econ. Council letter 2/1/67, 2/6/67 (Page A 467)
    - What is a Cop by Jack Webb, 2/6/67 (Page A471)
    - Is Kerr's Departure a Disaster by J. Kilpatrick, WES., 2/6/67 (Page A454-5)
    - Gentlemen, Think Again-- Our Tragic Rhodesian Error by Frank J. Johnson of the MANCHESTER UNION LEADER, 2/6/67 (Page A458-9)
    - How Much Should a Corporation Earn by J. Scanlon in the HARVARD BUSINESS REVIEW., 2/7/67 (Page H1065)
    - Neil McElroy's address introduction by Oveta Hobby, editor of the HOUSTON POST COMPANY., 2/7/67 (Page H 1068)
    - Industry's Stake in Clearing Our Transportation Bottlenecks an address by W.M. Allen, president of the Boeing Co. before Society of Automotive Engineers, 1/11/67., 2/6/67 (Page H997)
    - The Wars that Nobody Seems to Notice, Ray Vicker, Wall StreetJournal 2/3, 2/8/67 (Page A532)
    - Mousse au Chocolat, 2 Art Hoppe columns., 2/15/67 (Page A631)
    - What We Can Afford, editorial in the Wall Street Journal, 2/9/67., 2/15/67 (Page A646)
    - NATO, an address by Gen. Alfred M. Gruenther before the Commonwealth Club, 2/16/67 (Page A691)
    - NATO, AN ADDRESS BY Gen. A.M. Gruenther before the Commonwealth Club of San Francisco., 2/16/67 (Page A691)
    - B.G. Chas. Meyer Says Dissenters Here in the U.S. Might Have Blood on their hands, and address before the Commonwealth Club., 2/20/67 (Page A730)
    - Increase in GNP Described as More Fat Than Muscle, an Article by John Cunniff in The Washington Star., 2/20/67 (Page A735)
    - Dollars and Cents and Rhodesia by Charles Bartlett, Wash. Star, 2/20/67 (Page A739)
    - The Sierra Club's Ironic Tax Exemption Case, an Article by J. Kilpatrick in the STAR., 2/20/67 (Page A745)
    - Lessons I Have Learned From Masons, an address by William Henry., 2/21/67 (Page A773)
    - Watching the China Watchers Elbie Jay Makes a Sacrifice 2 Articles by A. Hoppe, 2/15,2/19 CHRON., 2/23/67 (Page A835)
    - The American Interst in So. Africa an address by John Davenport., 2/27/67 (Page A1763)
    - Why the War on Poverty is Turning into a Rout, article in AMERICAN GOV'T., 2/27/67 (Page A883)